Guide to the Gerald Gillespie Papers SC0581
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gerald Gillespie papers
1930s-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gillespie, Gerald Ernest Paul
SC0581
37.25 Linear Feet
Custodial History note
Gift of Gerald Gillespie, 2000, 2005, and 2015.
Information about Access
None.
Biography
Gerald Gillespie joined the Stanford University faculty in 1974, teaching in German studies, comparative literature, and humanities programs. A recepient of Fullbright, Guggenheim, Mellon, and NEH fellowships, he has published numerous books and articles and served on the editorial boards of several journals, including comparative literature and German Life and Letters.
Scope and Content
These papers document Gillespie's professional career, largely from his years at Stanford University. The papers include correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, articles, papers, course materials, syllabi, and other items. They are arranged in seven groupings: alpha files (1964-1991), Stanford departmental files (1977-1999), Academic Council Committee on Libraries records (1988-1990), SUNY Binghamton files (1964-1974), University of Southern California correspondence (1961-1966), German Life and Letters files (1989-1997), and oversize materials.
The alpha files pertain to his own career and include correspondence, notes, typescript papers, reports, and other materials. Stanford departmental files pertain to the Departments of German Studies and Comparative Literature and include correspondence, memos, articles, syllabi, minutes, questionnaires, and other items. Academic Council Committee on Libraries records reflect his service on the committee and include agendas, minutes, reports, memoranda and correspondence. The SUNY Binghamton and University of Southern California files pertain to his teaching positions before he joined the Stanford faculty and contain primarily correspondence. The German Life and Letters files contain correspondence and typescript articles submitted for publication, with some minutes and reports. The oversize materials are largely posters and notices.
German literature -- Study and teaching.; European literature -- Study and teaching.; Comparative literature -- Study and teaching.; Gillespie, Gerald Ernest Paul; Prier, Raymond Adolph.; Stanford University. Academic Council; Stanford University. Department of German Studies
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-025
  - Alpha Files, 1964-1991
    - Alberta Report (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alberta Report (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Univ. of Alberta. Dept. of Comparative Literature. Self Study Report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Univ. of Alberta. Dept. of Comparative Literature. Self Study Report Appendices, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Univ. of Alberta. Campus Reviews, Third Edition, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Arcadia (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Academic (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alliance Francaise (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alabama (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Amherst (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anales Galdosianos (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - AATG (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - AAUP (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Association of Departments of Foreign Languages (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - ADFL Conference packet (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - American Society for Eighteenth-Century Studies (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WECS "Savage Places", Feb. 20, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Arbitrium (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Austria (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Atheneum (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - American Translators Association (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Aurora (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Australia (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Berkeley (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Boundary 2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Berliner Wiss. Gesellschaft (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Brown University (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Bucknell Review (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - California (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Caltech (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Cambridge, Univ. of (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Canada, Humanities Research Council (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - CUA Accreditation (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Catholic University of American (press) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Case Western Reserve (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Centre Culturel Allemand (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Comparative Criticism (C.U.P.) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Comp Lit (journal), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Columbia (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Canada (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Canadian Review of Comp. Lit. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - [Comparative Literature, journal] Yang: "King Lear" mss (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Comp. Lit. Studies (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Cornell (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Council on National Literatures (RNL) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Congresso Galdosiano (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Council on National Literatures (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Cuadernos Hispanoamericanos (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Curtis Brown (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Delaware (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Davis (Univ. of California) (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Daphnis (journal) (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - DVLG (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Diacritics (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Drama Survey (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - English Speaking Union (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Emory (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Exxon Foundation / NEH (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - FILLM (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - FIT (Federation Internationale des Traducteurs) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Florida State University 9th Conf., Jan. 26, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Florida State University Comp. Lit. Symposium (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - FSU (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - FSU Press (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Language Association of Chairmen and Supervisors (FLACS) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Georgia (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Germanistik Niemeyer (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - German Quarterly (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - German Consulate (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - German Life and Letters (GLL) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Germanic Review (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Germanic Studies in America (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Gorres - Gesells (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Goethe yearbook (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Guggenheim, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Gillespie Guggenheim (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - George Mason (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Harvard, 1988 ff (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Hawaii (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Historians of Early Modern Europe (HEME) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Hispania (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Humboldt (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Hispanic Review (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Institute for Renaissance Interdisciplinary Studies (IRIS) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Illinois (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Impossibility of Comparative Literature" keynote address at conference, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Indiana University, 1966-74 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Bloomington [Indiana University], 1982-89 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Inter Muse (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Int. Arbeitskreis (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Internationales Archiv Fur Sozialgeschichte der deutschen Literatur (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Int. Exchange / I. I. E. Fulbright (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - IDV (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - IVG, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - IVG, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - International Society for the History of Rhetoric (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - International Society for the History of Rhetoric (Rhetoric Group) (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - ISECS - 6th congress, July 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Jahrbuch f. Int. Germanistik (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - JAAC (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Japan (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - JGE (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Journal of Intercultural Studies (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Journal of English and Germanic Philology (JEGP) (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Johns Hopkins (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Kentucky (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Kenyon Review (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Lehman College (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Komparatisdische Hefte (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Lessing Yearbook (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - London (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Littauer (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Maryland (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Massachusetts (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Miami (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Michigan (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Minnesota (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Missouri (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - M.I.D. G. Wellwarth (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Monatshefte (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Monterey Institute (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Munich (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Modern Language Notes (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - NEH Resident Fellow (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - NEH, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - NEH Summer Research and Sabbatical, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - NEH Summer Seminar (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - NEH (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - NEH Interprofessional Seminar (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - National Humanities Center (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Northeast Modern Language Association (NEMLA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - NEMLA business, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Neohelicon (Budapest) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Neophilologus (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Nevada (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - New Hampshire (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - New Journals & publishers (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - New York (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - NYU, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - NYU, Sept/Oct 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - NYU (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Niemeyer Festschrift Account (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - [North Carolina] Chapel Hill (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Oberlin (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Ohio (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - W. Georg Olms (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Orbis Litt (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Oregon (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Philological Association of the Pacific Coast (PAPC) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Penn (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Paintbrush (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Univ. of Penn (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Univ. of Pittsburgh (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Pitt Press (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Princeton UP (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Purdue (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Princeton (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Renaissance Quarterly (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Renaissance Society of America (RSA), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Renaissance Society of America, Mar. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Renaissance Conference, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - RSA Arizona, Mar. 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - RSA Cambridge, MA, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Research in African Literatures (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Revue de Litt. Comparée (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Rhetorik (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Rockefeller (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Rockefeller/Bellagio (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Romance Quarterly (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Rutgers (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Rocky Mountain Modern Language Association (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Society for Renaissance Studies (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Seminar (Canada) (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Sprachkunst (Austria) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Southern Comparative Literature Association (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Society for German Renaissance and Baroque Literature (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Stanford French Studies and Stanford French Review (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Studies in Short Fiction (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Studia Neophilologia (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Sulmona (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - SUNY Press (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Stony Brook (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Texas (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Texas Tech (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - UCLA (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - USC, after 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Unterrichtspraxis (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Utah (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Vanderbilt / Cincinnati (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Virginia (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Washington (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Western Association for German Studies (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Weimer (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Wilson Center (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - World Lit Today (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Yearbook Comp Gen Lit (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Yale (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Yale (Baroque Conference), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - York (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Departmental Files
    - Artist-in-Residence (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Whiting / Lurcy fellowships (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - M. McLeod Lewis Fund; Danforth Foundation (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Visitors (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Stanford colleagues in M.A. and Renaissance (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Media (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Feminae Clarissimae, 1980-81 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - German Studies, relations with other groups (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Modernist (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - English (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Carolingian (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - German Student Council (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Schneewittchen and die 7 Zwerglein (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Applications (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Foeminae Problematicae (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - SGS Series (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Job Bureau (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Bonn (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Qualifying Paper (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Foeminae Cl. 1981-82 canvass (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Standing Committee, 1977-82 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - GS Budget (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Grad. Student schedules (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - NEH renewal (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - T. Andersson (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Frank, P. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Golring, Peggy (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Translators and Interpreters Program (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Lohnes, Walter (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Mahrholz, Gertrude (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Berman, Russell (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mason, Ann (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Robinson, Orrin W. (review 1982) (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Wellbery, David (review) (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Mommsen, Katharina (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Mommsen - Humboldt (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Mommsen replacement, 1980-82 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Mommsen Festschrift (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Muella-Vollmer, K. (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Robinson, Orrin (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Summerfield, Ellen (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Lohnes, Walter (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Cohn, Robert [news article] (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - A & P committee (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - [Wellbery - articles and reviews] (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Bai, Xiaodong (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Comparative Literature (CL) graduate students (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Western Civ syllabi (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Humanities Program students (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Humanities Program (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - G. G. Stanford (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - C-LIB report for 1989-90 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - CL Center & course materials (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gershkovich, Alexander, "Russian Romantic Drama: the Case of Griboedov" (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hilt, Douglas, "The Reception of the Spanish Theater in European Romanticism" (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Pladott, Dinnah, "Nineteenth-Century American Drama: A Romantic Quest" (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - G. S. Dept. letter to Campus Report, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Job description, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Undergraduate advisement (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Course Evaluation Questionnaire, December 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Graduate students, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Our students [includes photo of "Strothmann, Sokol, Reinhardt, Cooper, Petersen, summer 193-" place not specified] (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Central European Studies (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - GSLC; Interlit; Humanities Center (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Postdoc fellowships (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Ideas for grant proposals (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Fellowships/grants, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Minority student experience (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities - current policy (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - NEH - Dr. Susan Mango (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Translations (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Humanities 304 - completed questionnaires (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Job market for G. S. students (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Indiana U - West European Studies Program (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - American Translators Association (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Sponsored Projects Office (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - ATA Workshop (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Course revision subcommittee (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - German studies catalog review (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - German studies - advisement (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - CRIS (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous items (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - German Studies [G.S.] appointment matters (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Literature of Decadence (student's view) [photocopy of unnamed student's notebook from a course?] (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Dept. reading list - finals, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Graduate Studies (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Committee on Graduate Studies (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Committee on Graduate Studies (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - G. S. + University (1 of 3), 1990-94 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - G. S. + University (2 of 3), 1990-94 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - G. S. + University (3 of 3), 1990-94 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - G. S. department meeting, 5/23/90 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - G. S., 1994-95 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - G. S., 1993-94 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - German search public documents, 1993-94 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Language program G. S. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Reorganization " file, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Etchemedy/Shoven (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Report sheet (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Faculty search, 1994-95 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Job Trak (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, 1995-96 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Stanford German Studies Series (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stanford Humanities Center (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Mueller-Vollmer. Kurt (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Mueller, Magda (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Rasch, William (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Nolden, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Stanford C. L., 1990-94 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Stanford materials (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Mommsen, Katharina, 1992-94 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - G. S., 1992-93 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Stanford Continuing Studies (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - [Stanford] Daily (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda etc. re CIV teaching assignment (K. Mommsen and R. Berman), 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lanuage Center (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Stanford, current, 1996-98 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Graduate handbook (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Bernhardt, E. and Berman, R. "From German 1 to German Studies 001: A Chronicle of Curricular Reform." UP 32:1, (Spring 1999) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - A Guide to Graduate Study in German, Stanford University, Dept. of German Studies, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous department memos (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Academic Council. Committee on Libraries (C-Lib)
    - McManus (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, Aug. 1990, Sept. 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Misc. memos, reports, and notes (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - C-Lib agenda meeting of, Oct. 1989; Sept. 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - ACLS. "Scholars and Research Libraries in the 21st Century" (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - APC Action Team on SUL (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Publications on libraries (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Budget (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - C-Lib 1989-90; C-Lib Charge (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - C-Lib report, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Meyer renewal (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Centennial plans, SUL (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - C-Lib current (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Science journals (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Catalog debate (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - C-Lib Report 1988-89 (final) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - C-Lib, 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - rec.humor.funny - file A [re censorship of computer newsgroup] (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Administrative structure (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Budget repositioning (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - [minutes], April 10, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - C-Lib memos (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - C-Lib "Search" (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Departmental letters on SUL (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - C-Lib miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - C-Lib Report 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - April 9, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Feb. 9, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - March 9 & 21, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - May 1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - April 19 & 23, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Jan. 19, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Nov. 10, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Oct. 27, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Near West Campus (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - May 1, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Executive session, Apr. 10, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Mar. 6, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Feb. 6, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Nov. 21, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Nov. 1, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - May 22, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Dec. 14, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Gov. Docs. & Info. (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Automation (Bibliog. & Circul. Etc.) (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Computer Services (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Space (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Associates of the SU Libraries (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Preservation (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - rec.humor.funny (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - rec.humor.funny - consultations (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - rec.humor.funny - file B (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - First amendment issues (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - C-Lib handouts (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - C-Lib background documents (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Library Committee (Senate) (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - G.G. Xeroxing (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - SUNY-Binghamton Papers
    - German Department (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Personnel committee (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General literature (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Divisional personnel (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Harpur College, correspondence, 1964-72 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - SUNY correspondence, 1973-74 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - University of Southern California
    - Correspondence, 1961-66 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - German Life and Letters
    - Angermeier, John S., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Barry, David, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Del Caro, Adrian, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Gustafson, Susan, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Haselstein, Ulla, 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hicks, Steven and Krause, Edith, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Jensen, Birgit (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Kitching, Laurence (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Leventhal, Rob., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Lyon, John, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - MacKenzie, Paul A., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Pfeffer, Alan J, 1993, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ritchie, J. M. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Shookman, Ellis, 1995-96 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Witthoft, Heide, 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Zilcosky, John, 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Three papers (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Editorial Board (1 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Editorial Board (2 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Editorial Board (3 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Editorial Board (4 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Editorial Board (5 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1995-97 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1990-95 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Minutes, reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous items (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Oversize Materials [One Folder Filed With Other SC Oversize Folders]
    - Announcements of lectures by Gillespie at Emory University Princeton University Amherst College, and other unspecified locations, 1982, 1987
    - Posters from symposia and conferences that Gillespie participated in, 1993, 1999
    - Poster and program from a performance of Gillespie's translation of Der Gestiefelte Kater on the Caltech campus, [1983]
  - Restricted materials
    - Library Search, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Review Committee on: Turneaure, Petig, Chadburn, Eshel, 1984, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Curriculm and staffing needs report for dept. of german studies, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Evaluation: Sarah J. Poor, Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Admissions, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Butler, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Graduate student grades, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grades, Spring 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grades Sem I, Fall 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Grades, Spring 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)